A rich man lives in a big city near the sea.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: A rich man lives in a big city near the sea.]
He has got three daughters and three sons.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He has got three daughters and three sons.]
One daughter is called 'Beauty' because she
is very beautiful.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: One daughter is called 'Beauty' because she
is very beautiful.]
The other two daughters are called Rosalind
and Hortensia.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The other two daughters are called Rosalind
and Hortensia.]
They are lazy and unfriendly.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They are lazy and unfriendly.]
They like going out and having fun.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They like going out and having fun.]
They both want to find a rich husband.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They both want to find a rich husband.]
They do not like Beauty because she is beautiful.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They do not like Beauty because she is beautiful.]
Beauty has got long red hair.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty has got long red hair.]
She is kind and friendly.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She is kind and friendly.]
She likes staying at home and reading books.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She likes staying at home and reading books.]
She also likes playing the piano.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She also likes playing the piano.]
Beauty's father is a merchant.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty's father is a merchant.]
One day he loses all his money because his
ship is lost at sea.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: One day he loses all his money because his
ship is lost at sea.]
'My dear children,' he says sadly, 'I haven't
got much money.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'My dear children,' he says sadly, 'I haven't
got much money.]
We're poor.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: We're poor.]
We must leave this big house and go and live
in the country.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: We must leave this big house and go and live
in the country.']
'Oh, dear!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Oh, dear!']
say the two sisters.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: say the two sisters.]
'We're poor - this is terrible!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'We're poor - this is terrible!']
'What bad luck!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'What bad luck!']
say the three brothers.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: say the three brothers.]
'We have to work now,' says Beauty's father.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'We have to work now,' says Beauty's father.]
'Work?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Work?']
say the two sisters.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: say the two sisters.]
'No, we don't want to work!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'No, we don't want to work!]
And we don't want to live in the country.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: And we don't want to live in the country.']
They start to cry.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They start to cry.]
Beauty is sad but she says, 'Let's not cry!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty is sad but she says, 'Let's not cry!]
We can work and be happy without money.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: We can work and be happy without money.']
The family goes to the country and lives in
a small house.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The family goes to the country and lives in
a small house.]
Beauty gets up at four o'clock every morning
to clean the house and cook.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty gets up at four o'clock every morning
to clean the house and cook.]
Then she washes the family's clothes in the
river.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Then she washes the family's clothes in the
river.]
The three brothers work in the country.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The three brothers work in the country.]
Rosalind and Hortensia do not work.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Rosalind and Hortensia do not work.]
They do nothing all day.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They do nothing all day.]
They sleep all morning and walk in the woods
in the afternoon.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They sleep all morning and walk in the woods
in the afternoon.]
'I'm unhappy,' says Rosalind.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I'm unhappy,' says Rosalind.]
'I don't like the country because there's
nothing to do.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I don't like the country because there's
nothing to do.']
'We can't go to the theatre and wear nice
clothes,' says Hortensia.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'We can't go to the theatre and wear nice
clothes,' says Hortensia.]
'And we haven't got any friends.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'And we haven't got any friends.']
'Look at Beauty,' says Rosalind angrily.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Look at Beauty,' says Rosalind angrily.]
'She works and she's happy in this terrible
place.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'She works and she's happy in this terrible
place.']
Beauty's father says, 'Dear Beauty, you work
a lot and you're always happy.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty's father says, 'Dear Beauty, you work
a lot and you're always happy.]
You're a wonderful daughter.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: You're a wonderful daughter.']
A year later Beauty's father gets an important
letter.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: A year later Beauty's father gets an important
letter.]
He calls his six children and says, 'Listen
to this letter:'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He calls his six children and says, 'Listen
to this letter:']
You ship is here.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: You ship is here.]
It is not lost at sea!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: It is not lost at sea!]
Please come to the port.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Please come to the port.]
Everyone is happy.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Everyone is happy.]
'This is wonderful news!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'This is wonderful news!']
say the three sons.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: say the three sons.]
'Yes,' says their father, 'the ship with my
goods is in the port.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Yes,' says their father, 'the ship with my
goods is in the port.']
'We're rich again!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'We're rich again!']
says Rosalind.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: says Rosalind.]
'We can buy beautiful clothes.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'We can buy beautiful clothes.']
'We can go back to our big house in the city,'
says Hortensia.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'We can go back to our big house in the city,'
says Hortensia.]
'I must go to the port today,' says her father
happily.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I must go to the port today,' says her father
happily.]
'Oh, father,' says Hortensia, 'bring me some
new clothes and new hats.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Oh, father,' says Hortensia, 'bring me some
new clothes and new hats.']
'Yes,' says Rosalind, 'and some new shoes
and jewels.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Yes,' says Rosalind, 'and some new shoes
and jewels.']
Beauty's father looks at her and says, 'What
do you want, Beauty?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty's father looks at her and says, 'What
do you want, Beauty?']
'Please don't spend your money, father,' says
Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Please don't spend your money, father,' says
Beauty.]
'Just bring me a rose.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Just bring me a rose.']
Beauty's father gets to the port and finds
his ship.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty's father gets to the port and finds
his ship.]
But there are no goods on it - it is empty!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: But there are no goods on it - it is empty!]
'What bad luck!' he says angrily.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'What bad luck!' he says angrily.]
'I must go home and tell the children the
bad news.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I must go home and tell the children the
bad news.']
On the way home he crosses a big forest.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: On the way home he crosses a big forest.]
It is snowing and windy.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: It is snowing and windy.]
He is lost.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He is lost.]
'Where am I?' he thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Where am I?' he thinks.]
'Where can I go?
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Where can I go?]
I'm very cold and tired.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I'm very cold and tired.']
He hears some wolves and he is afraid.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He hears some wolves and he is afraid.]
Suddenly he sees a big castle in the forest.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Suddenly he sees a big castle in the forest.]
And there are lights in the windows.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: And there are lights in the windows.]
'Oh, good!' he thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Oh, good!' he thinks.]
'Perhaps the people in the castle can help
me.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Perhaps the people in the castle can help
me.']
He takes his horse to the stable near the
castle.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He takes his horse to the stable near the
castle.]
He knocks on the big door of the castle but
no one answers.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He knocks on the big door of the castle but
no one answers.]
He waits outside the door.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He waits outside the door.]
Then he opens the door and goes inside.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Then he opens the door and goes inside.]
He sees a big hall with a fireplace.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He sees a big hall with a fireplace.]
There is a long table with a lot of food on
it.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: There is a long table with a lot of food on
it.]
He is cold and sits near the fireplace.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He is cold and sits near the fireplace.]
'How strange,' he thinks, 'there's no one
here.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'How strange,' he thinks, 'there's no one
here.']
He is hungry and sits down at the table and
starts to eat.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He is hungry and sits down at the table and
starts to eat.]
Then he is sleepy.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Then he is sleepy.]
He finds a warm, comfortable bed and falls
asleep.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He finds a warm, comfortable bed and falls
asleep.]
The next morning he finds some new clothes
near his bed.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The next morning he finds some new clothes
near his bed.]
'How nice!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'How nice!]
New clothes!' he thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: New clothes!' he thinks.]
'A kind person lives in this castle.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'A kind person lives in this castle.']
He looks out of the window and is surprised.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He looks out of the window and is surprised.]
'It's not snowing and it's a beautiful day!'
he thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'It's not snowing and it's a beautiful day!'
he thinks.]
'And there are flowers in the garden.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'And there are flowers in the garden.']
He gets dressed and goes to the hall.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He gets dressed and goes to the hall.]
There are biscuits, chocolate and milk on
the long table.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: There are biscuits, chocolate and milk on
the long table.]
He sits down and says, 'Thank you for this
lovely breakfast.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He sits down and says, 'Thank you for this
lovely breakfast.']
He looks round but sees no one.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He looks round but sees no one.]
He eats and decides to go home.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He eats and decides to go home.]
He goes to the stable and gets his horse.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He goes to the stable and gets his horse.]
In the garden he sees some roses.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: In the garden he sees some roses.]
'Beauty wants a rose,' he thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Beauty wants a rose,' he thinks.]
He takes a lovely one.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He takes a lovely one.]
Suddenly he hears a terrible noise.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Suddenly he hears a terrible noise.]
He turns round and sees an ugly monster.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He turns round and sees an ugly monster.]
CHAPTER THREE - The Beast
'You're a bad man!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: CHAPTER THREE - The Beast
'You're a bad man!']
cries the Beast angrily.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: cries the Beast angrily.]
'You come to my castle and I save your life.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'You come to my castle and I save your life.]
You eat here and you sleep here.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: You eat here and you sleep here.]
And then you take one of my beautiful roses.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: And then you take one of my beautiful roses.]
For this you must die!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: For this you must die!']
Beauty's father starts to cry.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty's father starts to cry.]
Oh, sir, I'm sorry!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Oh, sir, I'm sorry!]
You're very kind.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: You're very kind.]
Please don't be angry with me.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Please don't be angry with me.]
This rose is for one of my daughters.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: This rose is for one of my daughters.']
'My name is not "sir'' - it is Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'My name is not "sir'' - it is Beast.]
Please call me by my name.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Please call me by my name.]
You talk about your daughters.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: You talk about your daughters.]
Then one of your daughters must die in your
place.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Then one of your daughters must die in your
place.']
'Oh, no!' says Beauty's father.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Oh, no!' says Beauty's father.]
'They're young and they don't want to die.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'They're young and they don't want to die.']
'Then you must come back here and die,' says
the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Then you must come back here and die,' says
the Beast.]
'I can wait three months.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I can wait three months.]
Do you agree to come back?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Do you agree to come back?']
Beauty's father agrees to come back.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty's father agrees to come back.]
'My daughters must not die,' he thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'My daughters must not die,' he thinks.]
'I want to go home and see my children for
the last time.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I want to go home and see my children for
the last time.']
Before Beauty's father leaves the castle the
Beast talks to him.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Before Beauty's father leaves the castle the
Beast talks to him.]
'I'm not had,' says the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I'm not had,' says the Beast.]
'Go back to your bedroom.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Go back to your bedroom.]
There is a big chest there.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: There is a big chest there.]
Fill it with everything you want and it is
yours.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Fill it with everything you want and it is
yours.']
Beauty's father fills the chest with a lot
of gold.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty's father fills the chest with a lot
of gold.]
Then he gets on his horse and goes home.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Then he gets on his horse and goes home.]
When he is at home he gives the rose to Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: When he is at home he gives the rose to Beauty.]
'Take this rose, Beauty,' he says sadly.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Take this rose, Beauty,' he says sadly.]
'Let me tell you about my terrible adventure.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Let me tell you about my terrible adventure.']
He tells his children about the empty ship
in the port, the castle in the forest and
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He tells his children about the empty ship
in the port, the castle in the forest and]
the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: the Beast.]
Rosalind and Hortensia are angry with Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Rosalind and Hortensia are angry with Beauty.]
They say, 'Father must die because you like
roses, Beauty!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They say, 'Father must die because you like
roses, Beauty!']
'No,' says Beauty, 'father is not going to
die.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'No,' says Beauty, 'father is not going to
die.]
I'm going to the Beast's castle!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I'm going to the Beast's castle!']
'No, dear sister,' say her three brothers.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'No, dear sister,' say her three brothers.]
'We're going to his castle and we're going
to kill him!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'We're going to his castle and we're going
to kill him!']
'No, that's not possible,' says their father.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'No, that's not possible,' says their father.]
'The Beast is very big and strong.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'The Beast is very big and strong.]
I'm old - I must go and die.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I'm old - I must go and die.]
But Beauty does not agree.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: But Beauty does not agree.]
She decides to go to the Beast's castle.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She decides to go to the Beast's castle.]
'No, father,' she says, 'you must not go.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'No, father,' she says, 'you must not go.]
I want to go!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I want to go!']
'Never, my dear Beauty!' says her father.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Never, my dear Beauty!' says her father.]
'I'm not afraid,' says Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I'm not afraid,' says Beauty.]
'You must live and look after my brothers
and sisters.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'You must live and look after my brothers
and sisters.]
They need you.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They need you.']
Beauty's father thinks for a moment.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty's father thinks for a moment.]
Then he says sadly, 'Alright, Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Then he says sadly, 'Alright, Beauty.]
You can go.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: You can go.']
Beauty's brothers are very sad, but Hortensia
and Rosalind are not.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty's brothers are very sad, but Hortensia
and Rosalind are not.]
The next morning Beauty and her father go
to the Beast's castle.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The next morning Beauty and her father go
to the Beast's castle.]
Inside the castle they see a long table with
a lot of good food on it.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Inside the castle they see a long table with
a lot of good food on it.]
Beauty and her father are not hungry, but
they sit down and eat.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty and her father are not hungry, but
they sit down and eat.]
Suddenly they hear a loud noise.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Suddenly they hear a loud noise.]
'What's that terrible noise?' asks Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'What's that terrible noise?' asks Beauty.]
'The Beast is coming,' says her father.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'The Beast is coming,' says her father.]
Beauty sees the Beast's ugly face and she
is terrified
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty sees the Beast's ugly face and she
is terrified]
'Oh, this Beast is really terrible!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Oh, this Beast is really terrible!']
she thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: she thinks.]
The Beast looks at her and says, 'You're a
brave girl.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The Beast looks at her and says, 'You're a
brave girl.']
'I'm very sorry about the rose from your garden...,'
says Beauty quietly.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I'm very sorry about the rose from your garden...,'
says Beauty quietly.]
The Beast looks at Beauty's father and says,
'You must go away tomorrow.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The Beast looks at Beauty's father and says,
'You must go away tomorrow.]
And don't come back!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: And don't come back!]
Do you understand?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Do you understand?']
Beauty's father looks at the Beast and then
at his daughter.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty's father looks at the Beast and then
at his daughter.]
'Oh, Beauty,' he says, 'please go home!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Oh, Beauty,' he says, 'please go home!]
Let me stay here!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Let me stay here!']
'No, father,' says Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'No, father,' says Beauty.]
'We must be brave.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'We must be brave.]
We're both tired - let's go and sleep now.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: We're both tired - let's go and sleep now.]
Tomorrow morning you can go home to my brothers
and sisters.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Tomorrow morning you can go home to my brothers
and sisters.']
That night Beauty has a dream.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: That night Beauty has a dream.]
In her dream a good fairy says,
'You're a good girl, Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: In her dream a good fairy says,
'You're a good girl, Beauty.]
And you've got a kind heart.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: And you've got a kind heart.]
You want to save your father's life.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: You want to save your father's life.]
You're going to be very happy one day.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: You're going to be very happy one day.']
CHAPTER FOUR - Life at the Castle
The next morning Beauty's father leaves the
[需要簡體中文翻譯: CHAPTER FOUR - Life at the Castle
The next morning Beauty's father leaves the]
castle.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: castle.]
He is crying.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He is crying.]
'Don't cry, father,' says Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Don't cry, father,' says Beauty.]
'Remember, I love you.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Remember, I love you.']
'Goodbye, dear Beauty,' says her father.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Goodbye, dear Beauty,' says her father.]
Beauty is terrified.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty is terrified.]
'The Beast is going to eat me tonight,' she
thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'The Beast is going to eat me tonight,' she
thinks.]
'I want to enjoy my last day.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I want to enjoy my last day.]
I'm going to visit the garden of the castle.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I'm going to visit the garden of the castle.']
She goes to see the big garden and she is
surprised.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She goes to see the big garden and she is
surprised.]
It is a beautiful garden with a lot of lovely
flowers.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: It is a beautiful garden with a lot of lovely
flowers.]
Then she goes to see the big castle.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Then she goes to see the big castle.]
She looks in all the rooms.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She looks in all the rooms.]
On one door she sees this sign: BEAUTY'S ROOM
She opens the door and sees a lovely room.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: On one door she sees this sign: BEAUTY'S ROOM
She opens the door and sees a lovely room.]
There is a nice bed and a mirror on the wall.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: There is a nice bed and a mirror on the wall.]
Beauty looks round and thinks, 'There's a
piano and a lot of books for me.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty looks round and thinks, 'There's a
piano and a lot of books for me.]
How strange!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: How strange!]
Perhaps the Beast doesn't want to eat me tonight.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Perhaps the Beast doesn't want to eat me tonight.']
She takes a book and starts to read it.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She takes a book and starts to read it.]
Suddenly she sees these words on the pages:
Welcome, Beauty!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Suddenly she sees these words on the pages:
Welcome, Beauty!]
You're the queen here.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: You're the queen here.]
Tell me everything you want.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Tell me everything you want.]
'I only want to see my poor father,' says
Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I only want to see my poor father,' says
Beauty.]
Suddenly she sees her father in the mirror
on the wall.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Suddenly she sees her father in the mirror
on the wall.]
He is very sad.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He is very sad.]
She also sees her home and Hortensia and Rosalind.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She also sees her home and Hortensia and Rosalind.]
They are happy without Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They are happy without Beauty.]
'The Beast is kind to me,' she thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'The Beast is kind to me,' she thinks.]
'Why am I afraid of him?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Why am I afraid of him?']
At 12 o'clock she has lunch.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: At 12 o'clock she has lunch.]
After lunch she goes to her room.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: After lunch she goes to her room.]
'What a beautiful piano!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'What a beautiful piano!']
thinks Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: thinks Beauty.]
'I want to play it.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I want to play it.']
She plays some wonderful music on the piano.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She plays some wonderful music on the piano.]
Then she looks at all the books in her room.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Then she looks at all the books in her room.]
Some of them have got pictures and others
have not.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Some of them have got pictures and others
have not.]
She takes a book about flowers and looks at
the pictures of different flowers.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She takes a book about flowers and looks at
the pictures of different flowers.]
Then she sees pictures of roses of all colours.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Then she sees pictures of roses of all colours.]
'Now I want to go to the garden and look at
the lovely roses,' she thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Now I want to go to the garden and look at
the lovely roses,' she thinks.]
She goes to the garden and stays there all
afternoon.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She goes to the garden and stays there all
afternoon.]
She looks at the flowers and feels happy.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She looks at the flowers and feels happy.]
At dinner time she sits down at the long table
and then she hears the Beast coming.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: At dinner time she sits down at the long table
and then she hears the Beast coming.]
She is terrified.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She is terrified.]
'Beauty, can I sit here with you?' asks the
Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Beauty, can I sit here with you?' asks the
Beast.]
'You're the lord of the castle,' says Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'You're the lord of the castle,' says Beauty.]
'And you're the queen,' says the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'And you're the queen,' says the Beast.]
'Can I ask you a question?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Can I ask you a question?']
'Yes, of course,' says Beauty quietly.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Yes, of course,' says Beauty quietly.]
'Am I very ugly?' asks the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Am I very ugly?' asks the Beast.]
Beauty does not know what to say.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty does not know what to say.]
She looks at him and thinks for a moment.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She looks at him and thinks for a moment.]
'Well, yes you are!' says Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Well, yes you are!' says Beauty.]
'But you're kind and polite.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'But you're kind and polite.']
The Beast looks at Beauty and smiles.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The Beast looks at Beauty and smiles.]
'You're right, I'm terribly ugly but I'm kind.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'You're right, I'm terribly ugly but I'm kind.]
This is your home now, Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: This is your home now, Beauty.]
Please don't be sad!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Please don't be sad!']
'Some men are handsome but they're not kind,'
says Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Some men are handsome but they're not kind,'
says Beauty.]
'I prefer you because you've got a good heart.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I prefer you because you've got a good heart.]
'Thank you, Beauty,' says the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Thank you, Beauty,' says the Beast.]
Now Beauty is not afraid of the Beast and
she eats a big dinner.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Now Beauty is not afraid of the Beast and
she eats a big dinner.]
The Beast looks at her and asks a question.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The Beast looks at her and asks a question.]
Do you want to marry me, Beauty?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Do you want to marry me, Beauty?']
What a question!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: What a question!]
Beauty is terrified.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty is terrified.]
'What can I say?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'What can I say?']
thinks Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: thinks Beauty.]
She is silent for a moment and then she says,
'No, I'm sorry I don't want to marry you.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She is silent for a moment and then she says,
'No, I'm sorry I don't want to marry you.']
The Beast is angry and Beauty is afraid.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The Beast is angry and Beauty is afraid.]
Then he goes out of the room and says, 'Goodbye,
Beauty.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Then he goes out of the room and says, 'Goodbye,
Beauty.']
CHAPTER FIVE - The Magic Ring
Beauty spends three months at the beautiful
[需要簡體中文翻譯: CHAPTER FIVE - The Magic Ring
Beauty spends three months at the beautiful]
castle.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: castle.]
Every day she reads books and plays the piano.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Every day she reads books and plays the piano.]
She walks everywhere in the big garden.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She walks everywhere in the big garden.]
She likes the tall trees and the flowers of
different colours.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She likes the tall trees and the flowers of
different colours.]
She puts beautiful flowers in the rooms of
the castle.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She puts beautiful flowers in the rooms of
the castle.]
Sometimes she makes perfume from the flowers.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Sometimes she makes perfume from the flowers.]
But the days are long and she is often lonely.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: But the days are long and she is often lonely.]
Beauty often thinks about her father, her
sisters and her brothers.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty often thinks about her father, her
sisters and her brothers.]
'I want to see my father again,' she thinks
sadly.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I want to see my father again,' she thinks
sadly.]
'And I want to see my home again too.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'And I want to see my home again too.']
The Beast goes to see her every evening at
dinner time, at nine o'clock.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The Beast goes to see her every evening at
dinner time, at nine o'clock.]
They talk about interesting things and are
happy together.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They talk about interesting things and are
happy together.]
Beauty is not afraid of his ugly face now.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty is not afraid of his ugly face now.]
Every evening the Beast asks Beauty the same
question:
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Every evening the Beast asks Beauty the same
question:]
'Beauty, do you want to marry me?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Beauty, do you want to marry me?']
And every evening Beauty answers, 'No.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: And every evening Beauty answers, 'No.']
One day Beauty says, 'Why do you ask me the
same question every evening?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: One day Beauty says, 'Why do you ask me the
same question every evening?']
'Because I hope to hear a different answer,'
says the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Because I hope to hear a different answer,'
says the Beast.]
'I'm sorry, I don't want to marry you,' says
Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I'm sorry, I don't want to marry you,' says
Beauty.]
The Beast is very sad.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The Beast is very sad.]
'But I'm always going to be your friend,'
she says.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'But I'm always going to be your friend,'
she says.]
'You're a wonderful friend,' says the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'You're a wonderful friend,' says the Beast.]
'And you are too,' says Beauty smiling.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'And you are too,' says Beauty smiling.]
'I know I'm terribly ugly,' says the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I know I'm terribly ugly,' says the Beast.]
'But I love you a lot.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'But I love you a lot.]
I'm very happy with you.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I'm very happy with you.]
Please, don't leave me!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Please, don't leave me!']
Beauty's face becomes red and she is quiet
for a moment.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty's face becomes red and she is quiet
for a moment.]
'In the mirror of my room,' says Beauty, 'I
see my poor father.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'In the mirror of my room,' says Beauty, 'I
see my poor father.]
He's sad and lonely.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He's sad and lonely.]
He thinks I'm dead.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He thinks I'm dead.]
My sisters are married and my brothers are
away.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: My sisters are married and my brothers are
away.]
I want to see my father for the last time.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I want to see my father for the last time.]
Can I go and see him, please?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Can I go and see him, please?']
'Yes, you can go and see your father,' says
the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Yes, you can go and see your father,' says
the Beast.]
'But I'm going to be very sad without you.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'But I'm going to be very sad without you.']
'Oh, thank you!' says Beauty happily.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Oh, thank you!' says Beauty happily.]
'Please don't be sad, Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Please don't be sad, Beast.]
I'm going to come back in a week.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I'm going to come back in a week.']
'Alright,' says the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Alright,' says the Beast.]
'You can visit your father tomorrow morning.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'You can visit your father tomorrow morning.]
But remember, you must come back in a week.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: But remember, you must come back in a week.]
Before you come back put this ring on a table
near your bed.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Before you come back put this ring on a table
near your bed.]
It's a magic ring.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: It's a magic ring.]
Goodbye, Beauty.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Goodbye, Beauty.']
CHAPTER SIX - The Sisters' Plan
The next morning Beauty wakes up in her bedroom
[需要簡體中文翻譯: CHAPTER SIX - The Sisters' Plan
The next morning Beauty wakes up in her bedroom]
in her father's house.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: in her father's house.]
She gets up and goes downstairs.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She gets up and goes downstairs.]
When her father sees her he cries, 'Beauty,
is that you?
[需要簡體中文翻譯: When her father sees her he cries, 'Beauty,
is that you?]
How wonderful!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: How wonderful!]
My daughter is well and she's here!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: My daughter is well and she's here!']
Beauty is very happy and hugs her father.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty is very happy and hugs her father.]
'Get dressed quickly and then tell me about
the Beast!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Get dressed quickly and then tell me about
the Beast!']
says her father happily.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: says her father happily.]
She goes to her room and finds a chest full
of beautiful clothes.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She goes to her room and finds a chest full
of beautiful clothes.]
'This is a present from the Beast!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'This is a present from the Beast!']
says Beauty to her father.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: says Beauty to her father.]
He's very nice and gives me presents every
day.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He's very nice and gives me presents every
day.']
She chooses some lovely clothes.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She chooses some lovely clothes.]
'I want to give these lovely clothes to Rosalind
and Hortensia,' she says.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I want to give these lovely clothes to Rosalind
and Hortensia,' she says.]
When she says this the chest disappears!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: When she says this the chest disappears!]
'The Beast is watching you,' says Beauty's
father.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'The Beast is watching you,' says Beauty's
father.]
'These beautiful clothes are for you and not
for your sisters.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'These beautiful clothes are for you and not
for your sisters.']
Suddenly the chest comes back again.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Suddenly the chest comes back again.]
That morning Rosalind and Hortensia come to
visit their sister.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: That morning Rosalind and Hortensia come to
visit their sister.]
They are both very unhappy.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They are both very unhappy.]
'Oh, Beauty,' says Rosalind, 'I'm unhappy.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Oh, Beauty,' says Rosalind, 'I'm unhappy.']
'Why are you unhappy, Rosalind?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Why are you unhappy, Rosalind?']
asks Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: asks Beauty.]
'Oh, it's a long story,' says Rosalind.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Oh, it's a long story,' says Rosalind.]
'Please tell me,' says Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Please tell me,' says Beauty.]
'My husband is handsome and he spends all
day in front of a mirror.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'My husband is handsome and he spends all
day in front of a mirror.]
He never looks at me or talks to me.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He never looks at me or talks to me.']
'Oh, dear, that's a big problem,' says Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Oh, dear, that's a big problem,' says Beauty.]
Hortensia says, 'My husband is very clever,
but he doesn't like anyone, and no one likes
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Hortensia says, 'My husband is very clever,
but he doesn't like anyone, and no one likes]
him.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: him.']
'I can never invite my friends to lunch or
dinner because he doesn't like them.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I can never invite my friends to lunch or
dinner because he doesn't like them.']
'We've got a lot of problems with our husbands,'
they say.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'We've got a lot of problems with our husbands,'
they say.]
'My poor sisters!' says Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'My poor sisters!' says Beauty.]
'I'm very sorry.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I'm very sorry.']
'Tell us about the Beast,' says Hortensia.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Tell us about the Beast,' says Hortensia.]
Oh, the Beast is not a bad man,' says Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Oh, the Beast is not a bad man,' says Beauty.]
'He's very kind.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'He's very kind.]
I live in his beautiful castle and I'm the
queen.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I live in his beautiful castle and I'm the
queen.]
I don't work.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I don't work.]
I read, play the piano and walk in the garden.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I read, play the piano and walk in the garden.]
Every evening the Beast comes to see me at
dinner and we talk about a lot of things.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Every evening the Beast comes to see me at
dinner and we talk about a lot of things.]
It's wonderful.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: It's wonderful.']
The two sisters are very angry and they go
to the garden.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The two sisters are very angry and they go
to the garden.]
'Beauty wears lovely clothes and shoes,' says
Rosalind.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Beauty wears lovely clothes and shoes,' says
Rosalind.]
'She's like a queen.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'She's like a queen.]
She's very happy.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She's very happy.]
Why is she lucky?
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Why is she lucky?]
And why are we unlucky?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: And why are we unlucky?']
'You're right, Rosalind,' says Hortensia.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'You're right, Rosalind,' says Hortensia.]
'We're not very lucky.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'We're not very lucky.]
But maybe we can be lucky!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: But maybe we can be lucky!]
Beauty has to return to the Beast in a week,
or he's going to get angry and eat her!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty has to return to the Beast in a week,
or he's going to get angry and eat her!']
'Then we must keep her here,' says Rosalind.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Then we must keep her here,' says Rosalind.]
'Then the Beast is going to get angry.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Then the Beast is going to get angry.']
During the week the two sisters are kind to
Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: During the week the two sisters are kind to
Beauty.]
They talk and laugh with her.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They talk and laugh with her.]
They walk together in the country.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They walk together in the country.]
Beauty is happy with her sisters.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty is happy with her sisters.]
'Rosalind and Hortensia love me,' she thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Rosalind and Hortensia love me,' she thinks.]
'They're good sisters and I love them a lot.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'They're good sisters and I love them a lot.']
At the end of the week Beauty says, 'I must
go back to the Beast's castle.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: At the end of the week Beauty says, 'I must
go back to the Beast's castle.']
But her sisters start to cry.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: But her sisters start to cry.]
'Oh, Beauty,' says Rosalind, 'please stay
with us another week.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Oh, Beauty,' says Rosalind, 'please stay
with us another week.]
We need you.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: We need you.']
'Yes, Beauty,' says Hortensia, 'please don't
leave us.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Yes, Beauty,' says Hortensia, 'please don't
leave us.]
We have fun with you and we love you.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: We have fun with you and we love you.']
'Yes,' says Rosalind, 'stay with us!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Yes,' says Rosalind, 'stay with us!]
We can do a lot of things together.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: We can do a lot of things together.']
Beauty does not know what to do.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty does not know what to do.]
She decides to stay another week.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She decides to stay another week.]
CHAPTER SEVEN - The Dream
The Beast is going to be very sad without
[需要簡體中文翻譯: CHAPTER SEVEN - The Dream
The Beast is going to be very sad without]
me,' Beauty thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: me,' Beauty thinks.]
'But I want to stay with my family for a few
more days.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'But I want to stay with my family for a few
more days.]
Then I'm going to go back to him.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Then I'm going to go back to him.']
Beauty thinks about the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty thinks about the Beast.]
She misses him.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She misses him.]
Ten days later Beauty dreams about the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Ten days later Beauty dreams about the Beast.]
In her dream the Beast is on the grass in
the garden of the castle.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: In her dream the Beast is on the grass in
the garden of the castle.]
And he's going to die!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: And he's going to die!]
'Beauty, whispers the Beast, 'today is the
tenth day and you're not here.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Beauty, whispers the Beast, 'today is the
tenth day and you're not here.]
I can't live without you.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I can't live without you.]
I can't eat or drink.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I can't eat or drink.']
Beauty wakes up and thinks, 'The poor Beast
is going to die without me!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty wakes up and thinks, 'The poor Beast
is going to die without me!]
I must go back to him.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I must go back to him.']
She takes the ring and puts it on a table
near her bed.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She takes the ring and puts it on a table
near her bed.]
'The Beast is ugly but he's very kind,' she
thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'The Beast is ugly but he's very kind,' she
thinks.]
'Why don't I marry him?
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Why don't I marry him?]
I'm happy with him.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I'm happy with him.]
My sisters have handsome, clever husbands
- but they're not happy.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: My sisters have handsome, clever husbands
- but they're not happy.']
Beauty falls asleep and the next morning she
wakes up at the Beast's castle.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty falls asleep and the next morning she
wakes up at the Beast's castle.]
Today I'm going to wear a beautiful dress,'
Beauty thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Today I'm going to wear a beautiful dress,'
Beauty thinks.]
At nine o'clock in the evening she goes to
dinner and waits for the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: At nine o'clock in the evening she goes to
dinner and waits for the Beast.]
But he doesn't come to see her.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: But he doesn't come to see her.]
'What's happening?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'What's happening?']
Beauty thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty thinks.]
'Where's the Beast?
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Where's the Beast?]
Why isn't he here?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Why isn't he here?']
'Beast!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Beast!']
she cries.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: she cries.]
'Beast, where are you!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Beast, where are you!]
Answer me!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Answer me!']
She opens the doors of all the rooms and looks
everywhere in the castle.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She opens the doors of all the rooms and looks
everywhere in the castle.]
But she cannot find him.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: But she cannot find him.]
Suddenly she remembers her dream.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Suddenly she remembers her dream.]
She runs to the garden and sees the Beast
on the grass.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She runs to the garden and sees the Beast
on the grass.]
'Oh, no!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Oh, no!']
she cries.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: she cries.]
'Is he dead?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Is he dead?']
She listens to his heart and it is beating.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She listens to his heart and it is beating.]
'Good!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Good!]
He's not dead!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: He's not dead!']
she thinks.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: she thinks.]
She gets some cold water from the river and
wets his face.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She gets some cold water from the river and
wets his face.]
The Beast slowly opens his eyes.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The Beast slowly opens his eyes.]
'Beauty,' he whispers, 'I'm dying... but I'm
happy because you're here.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Beauty,' he whispers, 'I'm dying... but I'm
happy because you're here.']
'No, Beast,' cries Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'No, Beast,' cries Beauty.]
'Don't die!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Don't die!]
You must live and become my husband.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: You must live and become my husband.]
I love you and I can't live without you.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: I love you and I can't live without you.']
CHAPTER EIGHT - The Prince
Suddenly all the lights of the castle and
[需要簡體中文翻譯: CHAPTER EIGHT - The Prince
Suddenly all the lights of the castle and]
the garden, turn on.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: the garden, turn on.]
There are beautiful fireworks in the sky.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: There are beautiful fireworks in the sky.]
Beauty is surprised and looks at the castle.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty is surprised and looks at the castle.]
Then she turns round and looks at the Beast.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Then she turns round and looks at the Beast.]
What a surprise!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: What a surprise!]
She sees a handsome young man.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She sees a handsome young man.]
'Thank you, Beauty,' says the young man.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Thank you, Beauty,' says the young man.]
'The spell is broken!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'The spell is broken!']
'But where is the Beast?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'But where is the Beast?']
asks Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: asks Beauty.]
'I am the Beast!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I am the Beast!']
says the prince.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: says the prince.]
'I don't understand,' says Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I don't understand,' says Beauty.]
'Who are you?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Who are you?']
'I'm a prince and this is my castle,' says
the young man.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'I'm a prince and this is my castle,' says
the young man.]
'Sometimes a bad witch puts a spell on a prince
and only true love can break the spell.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Sometimes a bad witch puts a spell on a prince
and only true love can break the spell.]
Now I know your love is true.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Now I know your love is true.']
The prince takes her hand and says, 'Do you
want to marry me, Beauty?'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The prince takes her hand and says, 'Do you
want to marry me, Beauty?']
Beauty looks at the handsome prince and says,
'Yes, I do!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty looks at the handsome prince and says,
'Yes, I do!']
Beauty and the prince go to the castle.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Beauty and the prince go to the castle.]
When she opens the door she is surprised.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: When she opens the door she is surprised.]
'My family!
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'My family!]
You're all here!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: You're all here!']
cries Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: cries Beauty.]
She is happy when she sees her family.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: She is happy when she sees her family.]
They talk and laugh together.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: They talk and laugh together.]
Suddenly she sees the good fairy from her
dream.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Suddenly she sees the good fairy from her
dream.]
'Beauty,' says the good fairy, 'you've got
a kind heart and you're going to marry the
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Beauty,' says the good fairy, 'you've got
a kind heart and you're going to marry the]
prince and become a princess!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: prince and become a princess!']
Then the good fairy looks at Beauty's two
sisters.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Then the good fairy looks at Beauty's two
sisters.]
'You're both bad, lazy and unkind,' says the
fairy.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'You're both bad, lazy and unkind,' says the
fairy.]
'You don't love anyone!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'You don't love anyone!']
The fairy says some magic words and suddenly
Rosalind and Hortensia become statues.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The fairy says some magic words and suddenly
Rosalind and Hortensia become statues.]
'Oh, no!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Oh, no!']
cries Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: cries Beauty.]
'My sisters are statues!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'My sisters are statues!']
'Your sisters have got hearts of stone,' says
the fairy.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Your sisters have got hearts of stone,' says
the fairy.]
'Now they can't move, but they can see and
hear everything.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: 'Now they can't move, but they can see and
hear everything.]
When they understand their mistakes they can
become Rosalind and Hortensia again.'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: When they understand their mistakes they can
become Rosalind and Hortensia again.']
The next day Beauty and the prince get married.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The next day Beauty and the prince get married.]
Everyone dances and sings in the castle.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: Everyone dances and sings in the castle.]
It is a happy day.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: It is a happy day.]
People give flowers to Beauty and the prince.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: People give flowers to Beauty and the prince.]
The prince sees tears in Beauty's eyes and
says, 'Don't cry, my Beauty.
[需要簡體中文翻譯: The prince sees tears in Beauty's eyes and
says, 'Don't cry, my Beauty.]
We're going to be very
[需要簡體中文翻譯: We're going to be very]
happy together!'
[需要簡體中文翻譯: happy together!']